I can't believe we've never
done this. It's so good!
이 좋은 걸 처음 해보다니
너무 좋다
It's so good for Monica.
모니카는 너무 좋아
Time's up! My turn.
끝났다, 내 차례야
-That was half an hour?
-It's your timer.
- 그게 30분이라고?
- 자기 타이머야
I don't like to brag about it,
but I give the best massages.
이건 내 자랑 같지만
난 최고의 안마사야
All right, then massage me up
right nice!
그럼 까무러치게 해주세요
It's so good, isn't it?
너무 시원하지?
나한테는 너무 과분하구만
I don't know what
I did to deserve it.
시간 늘리려고 하지 마
Now stop trying to add more time
to your massage.
Say goodbye to sore muscles!
근육통이랑 작별 인사해
안녕, 근육들아!
Goodbye, muscles!
The One with Joey's Bag
She gives the worst massages ever!
걘 최악의 안마사야
It was like she was torturing me
for information.
고문하는 수사관 같더라
I wanted to give it up.
I just didn't know what it was!
실토하고 싶었지만
말할 게 있어야지
If it hurts that bad,
you should tell her.
그렇게 아프면 솔직히 얘기해
생전 처음으로 진지한
관계를 갖게 됐는데
For the first time,
I'm in a real relationship.
I won't screw that up
by telling the truth.
진실을 말해서
그걸 망치라고?
Dude, look out!
야, 조심해
You almost crushed my hat.
찌그러질 뻔했네
Sorry.
미안해
And the bunny got away.
토끼는 달아났네
This would be the place
where you explain the hat.
이쯤해서 그 모자에 대한
설명이 있어야지?
좋아
This is called a top hat.
이건 실크해트라고 하는 거야
And why are you wearing this?
Is it "top hat"?
그건 왜 쓰고 있는데
실크해트라고?
그래, 연극 때문이야
There's this play...
점잖은 국제신사 역을
따내려는 중이거든
...and I'm up for the part of this
cool, suave, international guy.
A clotheshorse. So I figure...
옷도 아주 잘 입지
오디션 지망생들도 모두
기막히게 빼입고 올 거야
...everyone at the audition will
wear ultra-hip, high-fashion stuff.
네가 걔네들을
다 사라지게 하겠다?
And you'll make them disappear?
넌 죽었다 깨도
이런 물건 못 찾아
Like you could find something
this sophisticated.
Done!
찾았다
조이, 그런 게 필요하면
우리 가게로 오면 되잖아
If you want to look good,
come to the store. I'll help you.
- 그래? 고맙다
- 별 말씀을...
-Thanks!
-Sure.
Please, take those off!
- 그것 좀 벗지 못하니?
- 네
Hey, Phoebe. How's it going?
- 피비, 별일 없지?
- 안녕
그저 그래
병원에서 오는 길이거든
Only okay because I just
got back from the hospital.
- 왜?
- 무슨 일이야?
Are you all right?
아냐, 난 괜찮은데
할머니가 돌아가셨나 봐
I'm fine,
but my grandma sort of died.
- 피비...
- 저런...
Phoebe, sorry.
It's okay.
괜찮아, 멋지게 살다
돌아가셨으니까
She had a really incredible life.
다시 못 볼 것도 아니고
또 오실 거야
It's not like I won't see her again.
She'll visit.
Maybe she's with us right now.
지금 우리 옆에 계실까?
너라면 새 삶을 시작한 첫날
커피하우스에 오고 싶겠다
Right. She's on a new spiritual plain
and she'll come to the coffeehouse.
얘들아, 저쪽 차 안에서
어떤 남녀가 엉겨 붙었어
I just saw two people having sex
in a car right outside!
Phoebe' grandmother just died.
피비 할머님이 돌아가셨대
어머, 미안해
Oh, my God! I'm so sorry.
괜찮아, 어떻게 보면
멋진 일이야
Actually, it's kind of cool.
Because it's like...
한 생명은 사라지고
한 생명은 만들어지고
...you know, one life ends
and another begins.
저렇게 해선 안 만들어질 걸?
Not the way they're doing it.
어떻게 된 거니?
어쩌다 돌아가셨어?
What happened?
How did she die?
할머니랑 슈퍼마켓에 갔는데
We were in the market...
요구르트 집으려고 구부리셨다
다시는 못 일어나셨어
...and she bent down to get some yogurt
and never came back up again.
이 일을 어쩌냐
I'm so sorry.
마지막에 이렇게 말씀하셨어
The last thing she said was:
'넌 달걀을 가져오너라
난 요구르트를 가져올 테니'
"You get the eggs, I'll get the yogurt,
and we'll meet at the checkout counter."
'카운터에서 만나자꾸나'
이거 아니?
우린 카운터에서 꼭 만날 거야
You know what?
We will meet at the checkout counter.
오디션 끝나면 반환할 거니까
속옷은 꼭 입어라
Since you're returning
all this stuff...
...you'll have to wear underwear.
알았어, 그럼 속옷도 보여줘
All right.
You'd better show me that too.
뭔가 허전한데
It's missing something.
알았다
핸드백을 들라고?
Really? A purse?
이건 핸드백이 아니라
어깨에 메는 가방이야
It's not a purse.
It's a shoulder bag.
여자 핸드백 같구만
It looks like a woman's purse.
아냐, 봄철 카탈로그에 보면
남자들도 다 메고 있어, 잘 봐
Trust me, all the men are carrying
them in the spring catalog.
어때, 남자지?
See, look.
Men carrying the bag.
메고 있잖아
이걸 봐, 여자들도 멨네
See, look.
Women carrying the bag.
But it is odd how a woman's purse
looks so good on me, a man.
여자 핸드백이 남자인 나한테
이렇게 잘 어울릴 수가 있냐?
거봐, '유니섹스'야
Exactly. Unisex!
'아이 니드 섹스?'
난 엊그제 했어
Maybe you need sex.
I had sex a couple days ago.
No, Joey. U-N-I sex.
그게 아니라
'유-엔-아이 섹스'라고
'너랑 나랑?' 그거 좋지
I ain't gonna say no to that!
- 누구세요?
- 피비야
-Who is it?
-It's Phoebe.
웬일이야?
Oh, great!
아, 너구나
Oh, you.
What's up?
무슨 일이니?
안 좋은 소식이야
들어가도 돼?
Well, I sort of have some bad news.
Can I come in?
어... 아니, 안 돼
No, thanks.
저기...
- 오늘 할머니가 돌아가셨어
- 저런
Grandma died today.
Didn't she die like five years ago?
5년 전에 돌아가시지 않았니?
No, she just died today.
아냐, 오늘 돌아가셨어
We're having
a memorial service tomorrow.
내일 장례식 치를 거야
난 분명히 할머니
장례식에 갔었어
Okay, I know I went to that already.
No, you didn't!
아냐, 안 갔어
그럼 5년 전에
돌아가신 게 누구지?
Then who's been dead?
그게 한둘이니?
Lots of people!
장례식에 올 거야, 말 거야?
Look, are you coming or not?
안 가
난 벌써 돌아가신 줄 알고
마음의 정리를 해뒀거든
I thought she was dead,
so I've made my peace.
내일 콘서트가 있어
Plus I'm going to a concert.
I'd invite you,
but I only have two tickets left.
너도 초대하고 싶지만
표가 두 장밖에 없어서
-Fine. Okay, enjoy your concert.
-Thanks. Enjoy your funeral!
알았어, 콘서트 구경 잘해
너도 장례식 구경 잘해
- 나 왔다
- 그래
아드님이랑 똑같이 생기셨네요
트리비아니 부인
You look just like your son,
Mrs. Tribbiani.
이 남성용 가방 보고 그러냐?
What? Are you referring
to my man's bag?
모양만 좋다고 생각했는데
꽤 실용적이야, 이걸 봐
I thought it just looked good,
but it's practical too.
칸막이가 아주 잘 돼있어
지갑, 열쇠, 수첩...
It's got compartments for your
wallet, keys, address book....
Your makeup.
화장품까지?
What are you doing?
The audition's tomorrow.
가방은 왜 들고 다녀?
오디션은 내일이라며
간식시간은 지금이걸랑
Yeah, but sandwich time is right now.
거기 겨자 묻혔다간
반환 안 되는 거 알지?
You get mustard on that bag,
you can't return it.
누가 반환한대?
나 이 가방 좋아
Why would I return this?
I love this bag!
- 그럼 350달러 지불해
- 알았어
-All right, then you owe me $350.
-Fine.
'바자' 카드도 받냐?
'무스터' 카드는?
Do you take Vasa or Mooster Card?
- 조이
- 긴장하지 마
Relax, I'll pay you with the money
from the job I'll get. Thanks to you.
이번 배역 맡게 되면 줄게
꼭 따낼 거야, 네 덕분이지
무슨 역인데, 아줌마?
What's the part? Auntie Mame?
Don't listen to them.
I think it's sexy.
신경 쓰지 마
내가 볼 땐 섹시해
'유-앤-아이 섹시?'
You-and-I sexy?
Hello, Mrs. Pinilla.
Thank you for coming.
안녕하세요, 피닐라 부인
와주셔서 정말 고마워요
입체안경 받으세요
Here's your 3-D glasses.
Reverend Pong will say
when to put them on.
퐁 목사님이 말씀하실 때
쓰시면 되요
나 왔어
Hi, sweetie.
견딜 만하니?
-How are you holding up?
-Fine.
그럼
피비, 힘내라
Hey, Phoebe. I'm so sorry.
어머, 할머니 가방도
이거랑 똑같았는데
You know what?
My grandma had the exact same bag!
꽃 좀 가져왔어
I brought you flowers.
Oh, thanks!
고마워
꽃까지 꺼내니까 가방이
훨씬 더 남자다워 보인다
Pulling flowers out
makes the bag look masculine.
실례합니다만
여기가 장례식장 맞나요?
Excuse me, is this the memorial?
- 네, 어서 오세요
- 안녕하세요
Welcome.
입체안경 받으세요
Here's your 3-D glasses.
이런, 네
All right.
프랜시스 부인과는
어떤 관계시죠?
So how did you know Frances?
실은 못 본 지 여러 해 됐어요
Actually, I hadn't seen her for years.
하지만... 두 모녀분과
아주 가까운 사이였죠
But I was pretty tight
with her and her daughter.
정말요? 성함이 뭔데요?
What's your name?
프랭크 부페이..
Frank Buffay.
못 들은 걸로 합시다
내 본명은 조예요
You know what? Strike that.
My name, actually, is Joe.
Joe Hill.
조... 힐입니다
You're Frank Buf
- 프랭크 부페이라구요?
- 쉿! 아서! 조 힐!
No! Joe Hill.
- 하지만 방금...
- 그만 가봐야겠군요
You just said
I got to go.
Thank you so much for coming.
와줘서 정말 고마워요
저기...
세상에
Oh, my God!
- 왜 그래
- 무슨 일이니?
What happened?
That was my dad.
저 사람 우리 아빠야
- 맙소사
- 뭐?
얘들아, 이것 좀 봐
Check it out!
It's like it's coming right at me.
진짜 다가오는 것 같아
-Did you catch him?
-What did he say?
- 만났어?
- 그래
뭐래?
He said, "Nice to meet you, Glenda."
이러더라
'반가워요, 글렌다'
I couldn't give him my real name.
내 진짜 이름은 도저히
못 밝히겠더라
그건 왜?
Why not?
달아나는 거 봤잖아
You saw the way he ran.
You think he'd talk
to the daughter he abandoned?
자기가 버린 딸을
마주할 수 있겠어?
넌 뭐라고 했는데?
What did you say to him?
내가 할머니 유언집행인인데
할 얘기가 있다고 했지
I said I was the executor of the will
and I needed to talk to him.
I'm going to meet him
at the coffeehouse.
이따 커피하우스에서
만나기로 했어
Could everyone take their seats?
모두 자리에 앉아주세요
I just can't think about that now.
그 일은 나중에 생각하고
I want to say goodbye to my grandma.
지금은 할머니 보내드려야지
그래
Let's go say goodbye.
그럼 들어가자
얘들아
I'm off to my audition.
How do I look?
오디션 간다, 나 어때?
Great!
That bag will get you that part.
근사하다, 가방 덕분에
그 배역 꼭 따낼 거야
And a date with a man.
남자들 데이트신청도
You know what? Make fun all you want.
This is a great bag.
그래, 맘대로 놀려라
어쨌든 이 가방은 근사해
And it's as handy as it is becoming.
발군의 실용성하며
Just because you don't understand
something, doesn't make it wrong.
너희들이 이해 못하면
다 잘못된 거냐?
지금부터 잘 적응해두라고
조이와 얘는 한 몸이니까
You guys have to get used
to the fact that Joey...
...comes with a bag!
나도 가봐야겠다
아빠 만나야지
I've got to meet my dad.
네가 누군지 말할 거니?
Will you tell him who you are?
Not at first.
I don't want to freak him out.
처음부터 그렇게 나가면
놀라실 거야
But aren't you pissed at him?
화도 안 나니?
널 버린 사람이야
This guy abandoned you.
If it were me, this guy would be
in some serious physical danger.
내가 피비 입장이라면
그 사람 무사하지 못해
I'd walk in there,
I'd be like, "Yo, Dad!
나 같으면 이럴 거야
'여보쇼, 꼰대! '
You and me, outside.
Right now!"
'나랑 맞장 한판 뜹시다! '
I kind of scared myself.
내가 생각해도 무섭다
Well, at least you scared someone.
오빠라도 무서워서 다행이네
You'd think I'd be angry.
화를 내는 게 마땅하겠지
머리통을 쪼개버릴 만큼!
You'd think I'd want to rip
his tiny, little head off!
Fortunately, I'm past it.
다행히 그런 시기는 지났어
You do seem a little tense.
Here, let me help you.
- 너 긴장한 것 같다
- 그래?
- 내가 풀어줄게
- 좋아
Get off!
아! 하지 마!
그만해
Stop it!
Why are you doing that to me?
너 대체 왜 이러니?
What are you talking about?
무슨 소리야?
As a masseuse and a human...
안마사이자 인간으로서
...I'm begging you,
never do that to anyone!
부탁하는데 너 절대
그런 짓 하지 마라
I give good massages.
나 마사지 잘해
I gave them to Rachel
before she got allergic.
레이첼도 늘 내가 해줬어
나중엔 싫어했지만
챈들러도 얼마나
좋아하는데, 봐
And Chandler, he loves them!
Watch.
좋아하긴 뭘 좋아해
아파서 죽으려고 하는데
He does not like it.
He's in pain!
-No, he's not.
-Yes, he is!
- 아냐
- 맞습니다요
-What?
-I'm sorry, but
뭐?
미안하지만
아야! 아야! 아야!
You've been lying to me?
나한테 거짓말한 거야?
어떻게 그럴 수가 있어?
I can't believe that.
너 기분 상할까 봐 그랬겠지
Maybe he didn't want to hurt you.
But the minute we start
to lie to each other....
우리가 서로에게
거짓말하는 순간...
And by "we"...
여기서 우리란...
...I mean society.
사회 전체를 뜻해
Anytime you're ready.
준비됐으면 시작하세요
네
Well, you must be new here.
여긴 처음이시군요
제가 한잔 살 테니 앉으시죠
Maybe we get a table,
I buy you a drink.
미안하지만 그 핸드백
놓고 하면 안 될까요?
Could you try it without the purse?
Yeah, sure.
네, 그러죠
Well, you must be new here.
Maybe we sit
여긴 처음이시군요, 제가...
Can I ask you something?
- 드릴 말씀이 있는데요
- 그래요, 뭐죠?
Sure. What?
Well, first,
it's not a purse.
우선 이건 핸드백이 아닙니다
알았어요
계속하세요
Anytime.
여자용인 줄 아시나 본데
이건 남자들이 쓰는 거예요
If you think
it's a woman's bag, it's not.
It's a man's bag.
Okay. And go!
알았어요
자, 어서 갑시다
Let me show you the catalog.
제가 카탈로그를 보여드리죠
이걸 보세요
Look. See?
It's the latest thing.
최신 유행이라
남녀노소를 가리지 않아요
Everyone's got one.
Men, women, children.
Do you sell these?
가방 외판원입니까?
아니죠, 이 녀석들은
영업이 필요 없답니다
No, these babies sell themselves.
됐어요, 수고 많았어요
Thank you.
That was great.
But I didn't read anything.
아직 아무 것도 안 했는데
I think we've seen enough.
그 정도면 다 본 것 같군요
좋습니다
그럼 다음에 뵙죠
All right, I'll see you.
우리가 해낸 거야
We got it. We got it.
Is Rachel here?
레이첼 있어?
아니
저기...
Listen, I just wanted to apologize
about the whole massage thing.
아까 일은 내가 사과할게
I really like them.
- 그 안마 정말 좋아
- 이러지 마
Please, stop!
We're supposed to be honest.
서로에게 정직해야지
I wish you could tell me,
"l don't like your massages."
그냥 솔직히 말해 줘
내 마사지가 싫다고
I don't like your massages.
난 네 마사지 싫어
See? It's no big deal.
거봐, 별 거 아니잖아
But now you're crying!
- 근데 왜 울어?
- 그래서 우는 거 아냐
I'm not crying about that.
I'm crying about something at work.
- 식당에서 일이 좀 있었어
- 뭔데?
My boyfriend said
he didn't like my massages.
남자친구가 내 마사지 싫대
괜찮아
뭐든 다 잘할 순 없잖아
You don't have
to be best at everything.
Oh, my God!
You don't know me at all!
기가 막혀서!
넌 나를 너무 몰라
좋아
You give the worst massages
in the world.
넌 최악의 안마사야
I'm crying here!
나 우는 거 안 보여?
Look, hear me out.
아니, 끝까지 들어봐
You give the best bad-massages.
네 마사지는 엉터리야
If anybody was looking
for the best bad-massage...
최고로 형편없는 안마사를
찾는 사람이 있다고 치자
...and they thought,
"Who's the best?"
이 방면에서 누가 최고일까
당연히 널 찾아올 거야
They'd have to go to you.
So you're saying that
if there was an award...
그러니까 네 말은...
최악의 마사지 상이 있다면
...for the best bad-massage....
Who would get that?
- 누가 그 상을 탈까?
- 당연히 너지
It would be you!
You, Monica!
And you'd get all the votes.
너야, 모니카
만장일치로
So they could call the award,
"The Monica"?
그럼 그 상 이름은
'모니카'가 되나?
Absolutely.
- 물론이지
- 좋아
I suck!
- 난 개판이야
- 그럼
Thank you for meeting me.
시간 내주셔서 고마워요
뭘요, 별말씀을
Thank you.
Come sit.
여기 앉으세요
Sit.
앉으시죠
Sit!
착석!
Alrighty.
Before we get started, I need you...
좋아요, 시작하기 전에 먼저
확실히 해둘 게 있어요
...to state for the record
that you are, in fact, Frank Buffay.
- 프랭크 부페이 씨 맞죠?
- 그럼요, 맞습니다
Yes, I am.
- 좋아요
- 그래서...
What did Frances leave me?
- 고인이 내게 뭘 남겼죠?
- 네?
That's why you wanted me to come.
그래서 날 보자고 한 거
아닙니까?
그래요
Yes, she did. She left you...
맞아요, 뭘 남기셨냐면...
...this lipstick.
이 립스틱이에요
이건, 그거 참...
It's used.
쓰던 거네
멋지군요
Cool!
몇 가지 여쭤볼게요
서류를 꺼내야겠군요
I have just a few questions to ask,
so I'll get out my official forms.
So question one:
그럼 첫 번째 질문이에요
You were married to Frances'
daughter, Lilly. Correct?
프랜시스의 딸 릴리와
결혼하신 게 맞나요?
Yes, I was.
네, 맞습니다
그렇군요
두 번째 질문
Question two.
Did that marriage end:
그 결혼의 결말은
A, 행복했다
A: Happily?
B: Medium?
B, 그저 그랬다
Or C: In the total abandonment...
아니면 C,
아내와 두 아이를 버렸다
...of her and her two children?
It really says that?
- 정말 그렇게 적혀있어요?
- 네, 보세요
Yeah, see?
I guess then I would have to say C.
그렇다면 전 C라고
대답해야겠네요
좋아요, 처자식 유기
Total abandonment.
그럼 가족을 버린 이유는?
A, 정부의 일급기밀이다
Reasons for abandonment:
A: Top-secret government work.
B: Amnesia.
B, 기억상실증
아니면 C
Or C: You're just a selfish,
irresponsible...
이기적이고 무책임한
구제불능 인간이라서
...bad, bad man.
I don't want the lipstick that much.
그냥 립스틱을 포기하겠습니다
Would you do me a favor?
그런데 부탁 하나 해도 될까요?
Would you give Lilly...
이걸 릴리에게
전해주셨으면 합니다
...that, please?
네?
When you see Lilly,
give her that note.
릴리를 만나거든 전해주세요
장례식에서 얘기하고 싶었지만
I wanted to talk to her
at the memorial...
...but I pictured her getting mad
the way you did, and I chickened out.
날 보면 릴리도 아가씨처럼
화낼 것 같아서 그냥 나와버렸죠
그 편지나 좀 전해주세요
I wrote her a note.
Give it to her, please?
But you came to see Lilly?
- 릴리를 보러 왔다고요?
- 그래요, 왜요?
Yeah. Why?
Lilly's dead.
그 분은 돌아가셨어요
She what?
뭐라고요?
She's dead.
- 돌아가셨다고요
- 정말입니까?
Are you sure?
If she isn't, cremating her
was a big mistake.
화장해버렸는데 아니면 큰일이게요
I can't believe this.
I just can't believe
이럴 수가
어떻게 이런 일이...
How?
Oh, my God.
어쩌다...
맙소사, 이게...
How long ago?
- 언제였죠?
- 17년 전이에요
17 years ago.
What about the girls?
그럼 딸들은요?
Well, Ursula is a waitress
and she lives in Soho.
우르술라는 웨이트리스예요
소호에 살고 있죠
And Phoebe...
그리고 피비는...
...is on this couch.
지금 이 소파에 앉아있어요
Yep, lipstick and a daughter.
Big day for you!
네, 립스틱에 딸까지
오늘 횡재하셨네요
Phoebe, l....
피비, 난...
저런!
It's just, I don't know what to say.
무슨 말을 해야 할지...
I just can't believe that you're
my daughter. You're so pretty.
네가 내 딸이라니
참 예쁘게 컸구나
Yes, well, that's neither
here nor there.
네, 그렇든지 말든지
Would it make you feel
better if I said...
지금 와서 무슨 소용이겠냐만
너희를 버린 건 정말 미안하다
...that I was very, very sorry I left?
It doesn't matter what you say.
It won't make a difference.
무슨 말을 하든 달라질 건
없으니까 그만 가주세요
So you can just go.
알았다
Well, you know, in my defense,
I was a lousy father.
굳이 변명하자면
난 정말 형편없는 아빠였다
-That's your defense?
-Yes, it is.
- 그게 변명이에요?
- 그래, 사실이다
이유식 태워먹고
기저귀 뒤집어서 채우고
I burned the formula,
and I put your diapers on backwards.
I made up a song to sing to you,
but that made you cry even more.
자장가랍시고 만들었는데
너희들을 더 울리기만 했지
You make up songs?
작곡하세요?
Well, no, just that one.
But it was stupid.
그때 한 번뿐이었다
엉터리였지
보자, 어떻게 하더라?
Let's see, how did it go?
그래, 맞다
Sleepy girl, sleepy girl
졸린 아가, 졸린 아가
왜 잠들지 않니
Why won't you go to sleep?
졸린 아가, 졸린 아가
너 때문에 아빠 못 잔다
Sleepy girl, sleepy girl
You're keeping me up
이거야
난 이런 일에 영 서툴러서...
I'm not very good at this.
전 잘해요
Well, I am.
Not yet. No.
그래도 아직은 안 돼요
나 왔어
오디션은 어떻게 됐어?
How'd the audition go?
에스텔 말로는 떨어졌대
Estelle said I didn't get it.
뭐? 너 준비 많이 했잖아
What? Why?
Joey, you were so ready for it.
그래, 나도 될 줄 알았는데
그쪽에선 내가 탐탁지 않나 봐
I thought so too...
...but the casting people
had problems with me.
What kind of problem?
이유가 뭔데?
To tell you the truth...
솔직히 말하면...
...they had a problem with the bag!
- 이 가방이 싫대
- 맙소사
You know what?
It was a stupid play anyway.
어쨌든 형편없는 연극이야
조이, 이제 그 가방 포기해라
It's time to give up the bag.
I don't want to give up the bag.
포기하기 싫다면 어쩔래?
I don't have to give it up.
Do l, Rach?
포기할 필요는 없지, 레이첼?
You think I should give up the bag!
너까지 그렇게 생각하냐?
진정해, 너한테 그 가방
너무 잘 어울리는데...
Joey, I'm sorry. As terrific
as I think you are with it...
아무렴
세상이 아직 너와 네 가방을
받아들일 수 없는 것 같아
...I just don't know if the world
is ready for you and your bag.
I can't believe this!
그런 게 어디 있어?
잠깐, 가방을 아예 들지
말라는 소리가 아니라
Wait, I'm not saying
you shouldn't have a bag.
다른 가방도 많잖아
뭐랄까, 좀 덜...
There are other bags
that are maybe a little less...
...controversial.
물의를 일으키는 거
Yeah, they're called wallets.
그래, 지갑이라고들 하지
너희들 말이 맞다
You're right. You're right.
This bag has become like a part of me.
그동안 너무 정들었어
내 가방처럼 말야
It's like...my bag.
안 들어가는 게 없어
It had a place for everything.
-Oh, man.
-What?
미치겠네
왜?
There's a whole series of pockets here
I didn't even know about, Rach. Look.
내가 모르던 주머니가
이렇게 많았다니, 이걸 봐
Ursula, I have the most amazing news.
언니, 놀라운 소식이야
우리 아빠를 찾았어
I found our dad.
Phoebe.
나 피비야
Your sister.
And I found our dad.
언니의 동생
아빠를 찾았다고
John Glenn? John Glenn is not our dad.
존 글렌이 무슨 우리 아빠야
No, I will not join you in the lawsuit
against him.
아니, 고소할 생각 없어
It doesn't matter that he wasn't there
while we were growing up.
우리 아빠도 아닌데
그 사람이 왜 우릴 키워?
He's not our father.
그건 배심원들이 결정하다니!
What do you mean
that's for a jury to decide?